<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="action_card_scan">Read Card</string>
    <string name="action_card_sign">Sign</string>
    <string name="action_personalize">Personalize</string>
    <string name="action_depersonalize">Depersonalize</string>
    <string name="action_wallet_create">Create Wallet</string>
    <string name="action_wallet_purge">Purge Wallet</string>
    <string name="action_issuer_read_data">Read Issuer Data</string>
    <string name="action_issuer_write_data">Write Issuer Data</string>
    <string name="action_issuer_read_ex_data">Read Issuer Extra Data</string>
    <string name="action_issuer_write_ex_data">Write Issuer Extra Data</string>
    <string name="action_user_read_data">Read User Data</string>
    <string name="action_user_write_data">Write User Data</string>
    <string name="action_user_write_protected_data">Write Protected User Data</string>
    ​
    <string name="info_action_card_scan">This command returns all data about the card and the wallet, including unique card number (CID) that has to be submitted while calling all other commands</string>
    <string name="info_action_card_sign">Depending on Signing_Method parameter defined during personalization, this command signs data using Wallet_PrivateKey</string>
    <string name="info_action_personalize">Personalization is an initialization procedure, required before start using a card. During this procedure all card setting are performed. During this procedure all data exchange are encrypted because it\'s usually done at the third-party factory.</string>
    <string name="info_action_depersonalize">This command reset card to initial state - erase all data, writed during previous personalization and previous usage.
        \nCommand available on SDK cards only</string>
    <string name="info_action_wallet_create">If the card has an ‘Empty’ state, this command will create a new wallet, changing a state to ‘Loaded’.</string>
    <string name="info_action_wallet_purge">This command deletes all wallet data. If ‘IsReusable‘ flag was enabled during personalization, the card changes state to ‘Empty’ and a new wallet can be created by Create Wallet Command.</string>
    <string name="info_action_issuer_read_data">This command returns 512-byte Issuer Data field and its issuer’s signature.</string>
    <string name="info_action_issuer_write_data">This command writes 512-byte Issuer Data field and its issuer’s signature to the card.</string>
    <string name="info_action_issuer_read_ex_data">This command retrieves Issuer Extra Data field and its issuer’s signature.</string>
    <string name="info_action_issuer_write_ex_data">This command writes Issuer Extra Data field and its issuer’s signature to the card.</string>
    <string name="info_action_user_read_data">This command returns User Data and User Protected Data (up to 512-byte each) and two counters: User Counter and User Protected Counter.</string>
    <string name="info_action_user_write_data"> This command writes to the card User Data and User Counter fields.</string>
    <string name="info_action_user_write_protected_data"> This command writes to the card User Protected Data and User Protected Counter fields.</string>


</resources>